To discuss the market part, I will
first talk to you about the insurance data that has come in.
Insurance stocks are a
declining stock. All the stocks have
formed inside. I would say that there has been a
slight rebound in the
latest data. In this, would you
like to play insurance or life like
SBI Life, HDFC Life or long life?
However, if we look at the data, then the strongest ones are
long life.
If I
talk about insurance first, then this is something. From the
beginning, the
combination of industries and companies, especially
general insurance, was upward of elevated
1003%. Generally, within general insurance,
valuations are always high, even if the comment
ratio is low, it is below 100%.
In the case of ICC Lombard, we know
that the management's view was that
basically, due to the acquisition they did,
their comment
ratio will remain in the range of 104 for one and a half years. But
going forward, they are very confident because no one is
focusing on more profitable business
and whatever the insurance business does,  There is a slight dent due to the segmentation that has become very
commoditized,
but I think other
verticals are growing very aggressively there,
they are adopting strongly and
bringing new product innovations as well, so they are getting very aggressive
in the healthcare space as well. So if
I talk about general, I think this
industry will grow because the awareness of insurance is
increasing a lot and we
see that the kind of purchases that are happening,
this is no high value added tax, whether it is cars,
devices like mobile, so
general insurance has a lot of use in all these.
Due to the increase in Medicare healthcare costs, people's awareness
is increasing here and
they are definitely exploring to take good innovative plans,
so we saw the same data, the
numbers of ICC Lombard are
very good and like New India
Assurance, till now we had seen that there was
no growth, but still there is
decent growth there, but in this space I would
prefer ICC numbers.  It seems that the
valuations are comfortable for three years
and in terms of life insurance,
no doubt we have seen that
these stocks have corrected for a long time but
here I feel that HDFC Life is an
innovator in terms of price value,
here the valuations are also getting comfortable,
which were earlier very expensive at 4.5 times,
so here it is quite comfortable now and
they have sustained the margins very well and will do
product innovation
and here also we are seeing that
growth is being studied, so I think
if someone has to make an insurance basket then I think
ICC should
play long for the coming three to five years,
so this is fine on life insurance pass,
Parthiv, we will discuss other sectors with you also.